[Music]
stop it
stop playing that horrible music I can't
take it any longer
no way this is what you get for sending
that swapbot to our house yesterday
you almost killed my bro your brother
manik had it coming he's the one who
stole my wallet
just stop it you're going to kill me
[Music]
Dingo did you hear something it sounds
like it's coming from the living room
what no I didn't hear nothing go back to
Sleet Sleet
it was probably just your imagination
[Applause]
[Music]
Doctor Robotnik what's going on it's Sonic
the Hedgehog he just showed up and
started playing that horrible music
quickly get rid of him [ __ ] I didn't
know there were other people here
it's juice and jam time
it's okay Doctor Robotnik he's gone now
oh thank God I was afraid my head was
going to explode from those sick tunes
i think I need to go lay down for a
minute
do you think one of us should go cheer
him up and how do you intend to do that
in face
i don't know I was thinking about giving
him celery with peanut butter on it
Dingo robot Nick hates celery he only
likes candy and refried beans
oh yeah that's right maybe you should
just try talking to him
he might listen to you because you're
hot Doctor Robotnik
what is it Dingo talk fast or I'm going
to robot size you twice
why do you hate music so bad
Dingo do you really want to know I do
then sit your large ass down and I will
tell you why
Doctor Robotnik hates music
[Music]
dad do you really have to play your
guitar at 2 15
in the morning I told you I have a big
math test tomorrow and the teacher told
us
that if we all get a's we get to have a
pizza party
i don't want to fail the test because
you kept me awake all night
Robotnik I think you should mind your
own business before I go
and get my belt you should be proud that
your dad is a world famous rock star
and as a rock star it only makes sense
that I spend my free time practicing
some sick beats
but dad you're not famous the only crowd
you ever performed for
were me and my friends at my birthday
party
everybody in the kingdom knows you suck
you don't know what the hell you're
talking about snotbag you're just a kid
i sell out shows left and right I'm so
famous
that I met michael Jackson last week no
you didn't dad
why are you lying about everything I'm
not telling you this to hurt your
feelings dad you need to admit you suck
and learn otherwise you will never get
better [ __ ] you
I'm a rock star and rock stars make
their own rules
[ __ ] I got to take this I bet it's my
boss calling me into work at applebee's
yes yes this is Doctor treber khan dr
Robotnik's father
uh-huh yeah yeah I can't play guitar
why do you ask huh no way you've got to
be [ __ ] with me you've got to be
[ __ ] my ass
oh my God are you serious why me out of
so many choices
yeah yeah I promise you won't regret
this decision sir Hedgehog I will give
the people the best show they've ever
seen
dad what was that all about well it
sounds like your dad
you know the one who wasn't a rock star
just got a gig
and not any ordinary gig that call was
from sir Charles Hedgehog
the brother of princess alina herself he
personally requested that i'd perform at
the princess's birthday tomorrow
in front of the whole kingdom I'm going
to go get an egg mcmuffin from
McDonald's
but dad are you sure you should be doing
this I thought the royal Hedgehog family
hates you
what if they're just going to humiliate
you in front of the whole kingdom
and then use your shitty music as an
excuse to execute you
i can't believe you would say that
Robotnik my own son
of all people that I thought would
support me I would think it would be you
don't even bother coming to the show
tomorrow but dad
don't hate at me you're not my son
anymore your hair looks like a [ __ ]
peanut
okay boomer
[Music]
welcome everybody we thank you all for
being here to celebrate this joyous
day princess sAleena's birthday
please enjoy yourselves and dance all
throughout the night
and [ __ ] sir knight where is my father
kevin the Hedgehog the royal king of
Mobius my lady
i believe he said something about
heading down to the local strip club
to foot [ __ ] and cheap sluffs that's
just like him
can't even be here for my birthday let's
host
a foreign who strings your special day a
world who strengthens your special dye
if you set
yeah yeah right Charles
[Music]
prince Charles I had to stop by goodwill
on the way here to find
appropriate outfit for the show so with
all due respect your majesty get out of
my [ __ ] face
wait whatever what matters is that you
already know
and that last yellow objects in that
outfit
you're going to go on any minute and oh
so get rid of the old man
this is the worst party ever I'm ready
to be done with it
stop the music as princess I declare
that this party is over
and ready to be amused bring out the
fool
fool what's she talking about she's not
talking about me is she
what domingo you think [ __ ]
are you telling me I'm just here for
everyone's amusement
my son was right you brought me here so
everyone could laugh at me
this isn't what we agreed on yo we don't
got a choice anymore
you may intend to go away into royal
families orders you'll get
i I'm not going out there you wanted to
if I was read
thank you today
[Music]
hello everyone my name is Doctor Trevor khan
i am Doctor Robotnik's father I'm not famous
yet but I will be someday
it's a real pleasure to perform here at
the princess's birthday party
nobody cares just play
[Music]
[Applause]
[ __ ] you Charles you did this on purpose
you only invited me here to
play because you knew I was bad
[Music]
dad you're back how did the concert go
what do you think [ __ ] I [ __ ] sucked
I'm going to eat some pizza bagels
and go to bed I’ve had enough of people
telling me i'll never be a rock star
[ __ ] it's prince Charles I bet he's
calling me to go back down there and
apologize for running off
hello yeah yeah it's me what
yeah okay yeah I understand
okay bye
well they told me I'm going to be
[ __ ] executed tomorrow
but that they can't do that of course
they can they're the Goddamn rulers of
planet Mobius
they're saying I played bad on purpose
in an attempt to humiliate the princess
on her birthday
which is [ __ ] but you can't go
against the royal family so yeah I'm
gonna die
but I don't give a [ __ ] I lived a long
life and at least I get to go out like a
badass
I’ve been to places people have never
seen I’ve done things in my life people
only wish they could do
no you haven't dad all you've done the
past 10 years is stay home and drink
beer
why are you lying about everything you
know what I don't need to hear this from
my own son
get your ass to bed right now but dad
I'm playing with my building blocks
does it look like I care Robotnik if you
want to play with something go play with
your [ __ ] balls instead I don't give
a [ __ ]
i [ __ ] hate you you're the worst dad
ever
[Music]
is
any last words before you are hung for
ruining my birthday party [ __ ]
yet as a matter of fact I do you can
suck my big sweaty boy
somebody stop him don't let him get away
my dad ran away into the forest and that
was the last time I ever saw him
you're lucky I'm telling you this Dingo
normally I wouldn't tell this to anyone
I'm only telling this to you because
you're hot
when the okay of heartache
is heavy
[Music]
and weariness to
the weight
i think of you and everything you
gave
so I could feel the rain
the roots beneath my feet
the threat that runs through me is all
the peace
[Music]
you